Get The App

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Modified: November 10, 2023

Introduction
------------

This Privacy Policy sets forth how information, including personal information is collected, used and disclosed in connection with mobile and online services operated by Jackpocket Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates, including but not limited to, Jackpocket Interactive Gaming, LLC and Jackpocket Gives, LLC (collectively, “Jackpocket,” “we,” “our,” or “us”), including but not limited to the Jackpocket lottery and casino mobile applications (the “Apps”), the gaming products, sweepstakes offerings and related services available through [https://jackpocket.com/](https://jackpocket.com/) (the “Lottery Website”) and [https://casino.jackpocket.com/](https://casino.jackpocket.com/) (the “Casino Website” and collectively with the Lottery Website, the “Websites”), and other mobile and online services that we own and control and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively with the Apps and Websites, the “Services”). By using the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not govern the data practices of third parties that may interact with our Services. Our Services may include access to third party content that we do not control. We recommend that you consult the applicable privacy policies of third parties whose websites or apps you may be accessing through our Services.

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our lottery [Terms of Service](https://www.jackpocket.com/tos/), casino [Terms and Conditions](https://casino.jackpocket.com/page/terms) and/or any other relevant terms of service that govern our product and service offerings, as applicable, (collectively, the “Terms”). By using our Services, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the practices described here, do not use our Services.

Your use of the Services and any information you provide through the Services remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms, as each may be updated from time to time. In the event of conflict between this Policy and the Terms, the Terms will control. 

Any questions, comments or complaints that you might have should be emailed to privacyrequests@jackpocket.com.

### **Information We Collect** 

We collect personal information you provide to us, usage and device information automatically when you access or use the Services, and other information about you from third parties, social media platforms, and other publicly available sources. The information we collect includes: 

* **Contact and Profile Data**, such as name, email address, phone number, physical address, social security number, and date of birth.
    
* **Account Data**, such as the username and password you provide to set up an account with us. If you choose to login to the Services via a third-party platform or social media network, we may collect information from that platform or network. 
    
* **Government-issued Identification Numbers**, such as a copy of your passport, driver’s license and/or state identification card, including your photo, passport/license/or identification number, and associated information.
    
* **Payment Data**, such as credit or debit card, or bank account number and routing number for the purposes of processing transactions at your request. We do not store your complete banking account number or payment card number.
    
* **Financial Data**, such as information about your financial accounts which may include the bank you are using, account type (checking or savings), and we may query and/or receive the current balance of each account at any point.  
    
* **Location Data**, including the GPS location associated with your device.  
    
* **Feedback Data**, such as information and content that you upload when you participate in surveys or contact us with questions, feedback, upload attachments, or otherwise correspond with us online or otherwise (including on our social media pages).
    
* **Audio Data**, such as audio recordings associated with calls made to us.
    
* **Automatically Collected Data**. We, our service providers and third-party advertising partners use cookies, web beacons/GIFs, pixel tags, embedded scripts, e-tags/cache browsers and other tracking technologies to automatically log information about you, your computer or mobile device, and your activity over time on the Services and other online services, including:
    
    * Device Data, such as your computer or mobile device operating system type and version number, manufacturer and model, unique device identifier, browser type and version, screen resolution, the IP address used to connect your device to the internet, device identifier (such as the Google Advertising ID or Apple IDFV), time zone setting, session time, browser plug-in types and versions, the website you visited before you visited our Services and location information such as city, state or geographic area, the number of times you click a page/screen or use a feature, the date and time you click on a page/screen or use a feature, and the amount of time you spend on a page or use a feature.
        
    * Online Activity Data, such as browsing history, search history, and whether you clicked on or opened one of our emails. We also collect information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from the Services (including date and time), search terms entered, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. Please note that Jackpocket does not respond to web browsers’ “do not track” signals or other opt-out mechanisms that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who use our Services. 

### Information we receive from third parties

We work with third parties to provide you the Services (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive from them any of the sub-categories of information about you described above in the section entitled “Information We Collect” (collectively, with the information received from third-parties, the “Collection Information”). The Collected Information may be combined with information from outside records (e.g., demographic information, navigation information, and/or additional contact information) that we have acquired in accordance with the law.

Jackpocket uses Plaid Technologies, Inc. (“Plaid”) to gather end user data from financial institutions. By using our Services, you grant Jackpocket and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution to our App. You agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/legal/).

Jackpocket uses Dwolla for the purposes of processing ACH deposit transactions. By requesting an ACH payment transaction you agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored and processed by Dwolla in accordance with the [Dwolla Privacy Policy](https://www.dwolla.com/legal/privacy).

In addition to the above, we may need to verify your identity before we can permit you to use some features of the Services. 

For purposes of verification, we may also collect from you other information as may be required to verify your identity and/or location in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. This can include date of birth and address verification.

### How We Use Your Information 

We may use the Collected Information:

* To provide you with the Services.
    
* To respond to your inquiries.
    
* To provide you with customer service.
    
* To provide you with services, products or information, or actions you request.
    
* To send administrative information to you, such as information regarding the Services and changes to the Terms, including through push notifications, email and text messages.
    
* To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, including through push notifications, email and text messages. You may opt-out of receiving these marketing communications by following the opt-out instructions on the communication.
    
* To verify your identity and account information, and to comply with applicable legal requirements.
    
* For our business purposes, such as data analysis; audits; managing our information technology infrastructure and risk, including fraud monitoring and prevention; to enforce the Terms; developing new products; enhancing, improving or modifying our products and services; identifying usage trends; determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns; operating and expanding our business activities; and protecting the interests of our company, our Services, and our customers.
    
* For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy

### When do we disclose your information 

Jackpocket does not sell personal information. Jackpocket will not disclose, without your consent, any of the personal information that it collects from you or third parties for the purposes of marketing or promoting third-party products or services. Jackpocket will disclose your personal information as communicated at the time you provide or we collected such information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy.

The personal information you provide may be disclosed:

* To our third-party service providers, to provide services such as payment processing, advertising, website analytics, fraud investigation, data analysis, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, account and user verification, auditing and other services.
    
* Where you have consented to disclosure, in which case all information that is disclosed will be subject to the recipient third-party’s privacy policy.
    
* To our subsidiaries, joint venturers and affiliates.
    
* Where we have a good-faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to accomplish one of the following, in which case such disclosure may be made without notice to you: 

1. protect against harm to the rights, safety, or property of Jackpocket, its Services, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law;
    
2. comply with legal and regulatory obligations and government requests (for instance, subpoenas, court orders, and law enforcement inquiries);
    
3. comply with our obligations and commitments to safeguard the privacy and security of the Collected Information;
    
4. detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; and
    
5. enforce the Terms, including investigation of potential violations

### Text Messages 

You may elect to receive text messages from us. When you sign up to receive text messages, we will send you information about promotional offers and more. These messages may use information automatically collected based on your actions while on our sites and may prompt messaging. To the extent you voluntarily opt to have Text notifications sent directly to your mobile phone, we receive and store the information you provide, including your telephone number or when you read a text message. You may opt out of receiving text messages at any time by texting “STOP” to our text messages. All the information discussed in this paragraph excludes text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties, excluding aggregators and providers of the Text Message services.

### Corporate Changes

In the event Jackpocket or all or substantially all of its assets are acquired, Collected Information (including your personal information) may be one of the transferred assets. Therefore, Jackpocket may disclose and transfer your personal information and other data to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of Jackpocket or the Services, including in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests or assets, or other corporate change (including in the event of a dissolution or bankruptcy), and in all cases, this may include sharing the Collected Information with prospective purchasers, investors, trustees, or other involved parties as part of the due diligence or acquisition or transfer processes, in connection with court proceedings, or in connection with financial transactions that Jackpocket may be involved in, such as obtaining investors or financing.

### Aggregated Data

We may create aggregated, anonymized or de-identified information from the Collected Information. If we do, we may use and disclose such aggregated, anonymized or de-identified information for any purpose. Aggregated, anonymized or de-identified information does not personally identify you or any other user. We may share non-personal information. This is information that does not contain personal information and can include user statistics.

### Social Networks

Jackpocket is not a social network itself, but we may provide links to social media sites to facilitate sharing with such sites. Your use of such links is at your own discretion.

When you interact with our Services through social media sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending upon your privacy settings, you should be aware that this information may become public on the Internet. We cannot prevent or control further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. Please refer to those third-party sites’ privacy policies and terms of use to learn more about their privacy practices, which we do not control.

### Cookies and Tracking Technologies

When you use our Services, we and our business partners may use cookies and other tracking technologies for a variety of purposes and to enhance your online experience, for example, by remembering your log-in status and viewing preferences from a previous use of our Services, for when you later return to the Services.

A few additional important things you should know about our use of tracking technologies (e.g., cookies):

* We offer certain features that are available only with tracking technologies.
    
* We use both session and persistent tracking technologies. Tracking technologies (e.g., cookies) can either be persistent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). You are always free to decline tracking technologies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Services. Refer to the help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling tracking technologies such as cookies.

You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from third-party websites that we link to and our third-party service providers that we have allowed on our Services that assist us with various aspects of our Services, such as [Google Analytics](https://www.oprah.com/cookies_and_tracking.html#anchor_section4). We are not responsible for our third-party providers’ use of tracking technologies.

### Advertising 

We may use certain vendors to serve ads on our Services, as well as on other websites, applications, and social media networks. In connection with the delivery of advertising, certain vendors, may collect information about you and your visits to this and other websites. That information may include your IP address, internet service provider, unique personal identifiers (e.g., email address), and the browser you use to visit and use our Services and other websites and applications. They may do this by using cookies or other tracking technologies. The information collected may be used, among other purposes, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand your usage of, preferences on, and visitation of our Services and other sites, social media networks, and applications tracked by such vendors. This notice does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or other tracking technologies used in connection with other parties' ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and ad services to learn about their use of such technologies. If you would like more information about these practices to understand your options for not having your information collected and used by such companies, please click http://www.aboutads.info/choices and https://www.networkadvertising.org/.

### Links

Our Services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of others, including our partners, advertisers, and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or these third-parties’ use, collection or disclosure of your information. You should check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites

### Options for Managing Your Personal Data

Access, update or delete information. If you registered for an account with us, you may review and update certain personal information in your account profile by logging into the account. You may also update your personal information, receive a copy of your personal information, or delete your account by contacting us at privacyrequests@jackpocket.com. 

These rights are not absolute, and we reserve the right to verify your identity upon receiving such a request. We may retain some information from closed accounts so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze, or troubleshoot programs, enforce the Terms, or take other actions permitted by law. If your account is terminated or suspended, we may maintain information to prevent re-registration, or for reasons discussed in this paragraph.

Cookies & browser web storage. Most browsers let you remove or reject cookies. To do this, follow the instructions in your browser settings. Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings. Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, the Services may not work properly. Similarly, your browser settings may allow you to clear your browser web storage.

Opt-out of marketing communications. If at any time you wish to opt-out of future promotional emails and communications, you may click the “unsubscribe” link in the email or otherwise contact us at privacyrequests@jackpocket.com. It may take up to 10 business days before you stop receiving promotional emails. This opt-out does not apply to operational communications, for example, confirmation emails.

### International Users

The Services are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to users in certain states in the United States. If you access the Services from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Services, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and the Terms, you acknowledge that you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. You further consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of your personal information and tracking technologies/cookies as described in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that we restrict transactions through our Services to certain states in the United States.

### Notice to California and Colorado Residents

#### **Scope**

This section describes how we collect, use, and share the personal information of California residents as a “business” under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and their rights with respect to their personal information, and how we collect, use, and share the personal data of Colorado residents as a “controller” under the Colorado Privacy Act (“CPA”) and their rights with respect to their personal data. For purposes of this section, “personal information” of California residents has the meaning given in the CCPA and “personal data” of Colorado residents has the meaning given in the CPA, but neither personal information nor personal data include information exempted from the scope of the CCPA or CPA, as applicable. Additionally, this section does not apply to information we collect from you in the course of communicating with you in your capacity as an employee, controlling owner, director, officer or contractor of an organization (i.e., company, partnership, sole proprietorship, non-profit or government agency) in the context of performing due diligence on, or providing or receiving products or services to or from, that organization. In some cases we may provide a different privacy notice to certain categories of California or Colorado residents, such as job applicants, in which case that notice will apply instead of this section.

#### **Personal information we collect and use**

The list below summarizes the personal information and personal data we collect and use by reference to the categories specified in the CCPA in California Civil Code Section 1798.140(o), and describes our practices during the 12 months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Policy. “Categories we collect” refer to the sub-categories described above in the section entitled “Information We Collect.” Information you voluntarily provide to us, such as in freeform webforms, may contain other categories of personal information or personal data not described below.

|     |     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Category of Personal Information/ Personal Data | Categories we collect | Category of Source | Business or commercial purpose(s) for collection and processing | Business or commercial purpose(s) for disclosure | Categories of third parties to whom we disclose |
| Identifiers | Contact and Profile Data, Account Data, Government-issued Identification Numbers | Directly from you or your agents<br><br>From other third parties you choose to interact with<br><br>From our service providers | To provide Services to you<br><br>To communicate with you<br><br>To verify your identity<br><br>To protect your account<br><br>To prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Marketing activities | To provide Services to you<br><br>To communicate with you<br><br>To verify your identity<br><br>To protect your account<br><br>To prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Marketing activities | Our service providers, including payment processors, analytics providers, other merchants<br><br>Other third parties that you authorize<br><br>Our business and marketing partners<br><br>Third parties as required by law |
| Commercial Information | Payment Data, Financial Data, Feedback Data | Directly from you or your agents<br><br>From other third parties you choose to interact with<br><br>From our service providers | To provide Services to you<br><br>To verify your identity<br><br>To protect your account<br><br>To prevent fraud or illegal activity | To provide Services to you<br><br>To verify your identity<br><br>To protect your account<br><br>To prevent fraud or illegal activity | Our service providers, including payment processors, analytics providers, marketing and advertising partners, other merchants<br><br>Other third parties that you authorize<br><br>Our business and marketing partners<br><br>Third parties as required by law |
| Financial Information | Payment data, Financial Data | Directly from you or your agents<br><br>From other third parties you choose to interact with<br><br>From our service providers | To provide Services to you<br><br>To verify your identity<br><br>To protect your account<br><br>To prevent fraud or illegal activity | To provide Services to you<br><br>To verify your identity<br><br>To protect your account<br><br>To prevent fraud or illegal activity | Our service providers, including payment processors, analytics providers, other merchants<br><br>Other third parties that you authorize<br><br>Our business and marketing partners<br><br>Third parties as required by law |
| Online Identifiers | Account data, Device Data | Directly from you<br><br>From our service providers | Provide Services to you<br><br>Protect your account<br><br>Prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Debug or repair the Services<br><br>Maintain reliability, quality or safety of the Services<br><br>Improve the Services<br><br>Marketing activities | Provide Services to you<br><br>Protect your account<br><br>Prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Debug or repair the Services<br><br>Maintain reliability, quality or safety of the Services<br><br>Improve the Services<br><br>Marketing activities | Our service providers, including analytics providers, marketing and advertising partners, other merchants<br><br>Other third parties that you authorize<br><br>Our business and marketing partners<br><br>Third parties as required by law |
| Internet or Network Information | Device data, Online Activity Data | Directly from you<br><br>From our service providers | Provide Services to you<br><br>Protect your account<br><br>Prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Debug or repair the Services<br><br>Maintain reliability, quality or safety of the Services<br><br>Improve the Services<br><br>Marketing activities | Provide Services to you<br><br>Protect your account<br><br>Prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Debug or repair the Services<br><br>Maintain reliability, quality or safety of the Services<br><br>Improve the Services<br><br>Marketing activities | Our service providers, including analytics providers, marketing and advertising partners, other merchants<br><br>Other third parties that you authorize<br><br>Our business and marketing partners<br><br>Third parties as required by law |
| Geolocation Data | Location Data | Directly from you<br><br>From your mobile provider or ISP | Provide the Services to you<br><br>Protect your account<br><br>Prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Debug or repair the Services<br><br>Maintain reliability, quality or safety of the Services | Provide the Services to you<br><br>Protect your account<br><br>Prevent fraud or illegal activity<br><br>Debug or repair the Services<br><br>Maintain reliability, quality or safety of the Services | Our service providers, including analytics providers, marketing and advertising partners, other merchants<br><br>Other third parties that you authorize<br><br>Our business and marketing partners<br><br>Third parties as required by law |

### Colorado residents' privacy rights

As a Colorado resident, you may exercise the rights listed below using our online webform to authenticate and submit your request at: [CPA Online Webform](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/048df61e-d7fa-4291-a10d-715edb5fcb76/6df02ee3-20aa-48da-b971-5654d25c8d38). The link will take you to an interactive webform that you can complete and submit to make a request. We will then use the information in the webform, and potentially additional information that we request from you, to verify your identity. These rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request for reasons permitted by law, including our inability to verify your identity. If we deny your request, we will tell you why we did so. If we deny you request or you are otherwise unsatisfied with our response to your request, you can exercise your right to appeal through the webform. We will never discriminate against you for exercising any of these rights. If you have any questions about submitting requests to exercise your rights, please contact us at [support@jackpocket.com](mailto:support@jackpocket.com).

**Right to opt-out**

You, or an authorized agent using the webform on your behalf, can opt out of the processing of personal data for purposes of targeted advertising, the sale of personal data or for profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning a consumer (as such terms are defined in the CPA). 

We do not engage in any such processing of personal data. Therefore, there is no processing from which to opt-out, though the webform does still give you the ability to opt-out of such processing.

Should we ever begin processing your personal data for any of the above-listed reasons from which you have a right to opt-out, we will seek your consent before doing so.

**Right of access and to data portability**

You can ask us for confirmation whether we are processing your personal data and to access any such personal data. When exercising your right to access your personal data, you also have the right to obtain such personal data in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible and to the extent disclosing such personal data does not disclose any of our trade secrets, readily usable format. You may only exercise this right to data portability two times per calendar year.

**Right to correction**

You can ask us to correct inaccuracies in your personal data.

**Right to deletion**

You can ask us to delete the personal data of yours that we have.

### California residents’ privacy rights

As a California resident, you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request as permitted by law.

Right to request disclosure of personal information we collect and share about you

You can request the following information about how we have collected and used your personal information during the past 12 months:

* The categories of personal information we have collected.
    
* The categories of sources from which we collected the personal information.
    
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling personal information.
    
* The categories of third parties with whom we share the personal information.
    
* The specific pieces of personal information we have collected.
    
* The categories of personal information that we sold or disclosed for a business purpose.
    
* The categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or disclosed for a business purpose.

**Right to request the deletion of personal information**

You can ask us to delete the personal information that we have collected from you, subject to certain exceptions. We will also notify any service providers and third parties with whom we have shared your personal information of your request. If you are using Paysafe with our Services, and you desire to have your personal information deleted from Paysafe, you must contact Paysafe directly to make such a request. Please note that due to applicable laws and regulations, you will be unable to use some of our Services if your personal information is deleted, including, but not limited to, ordering lottery tickets or playing casino games. As noted above, your deletion request is subject to certain exceptions which we may rely on where it is necessary for us to:

* Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us;
    
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity;
    
* Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
    
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law;
    
* To enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with the expectations of the consumer based on the consumer’s relationship with us;
    
* Comply with a legal obligation; or
    
* Otherwise use the personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.

**Right to ask us not to sell your personal information**

We do not sell your personal information. However, like many companies, we may use advertising services that try to tailor online ads to your interests based on information collected via cookies and similar technologies about your online activity. This is called interest-based advertising. The CCPA’s statutory definition of the term “sale” is broad and may include interest-based advertising. You can get more information and opt-out of the use of cookies on our Services for interest-based advertising purposes by setting your preferences on the Apps or our Websites. You will need to set your preferences from each device and each web browser from which you wish to opt-out. This feature may use a cookie to remember your preference, so if you clear all cookies from your browser, you may need to re-set your settings.

**Right to nondiscrimination**

You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination as prohibited by the CCPA.

**How to exercise your rights**

You may submit requests to exercise your California privacy rights described above as follows:

* _**Right to request the access and deletion of your personal information**_. If you are a California resident, you may submit a request to exercise the access and deletion rights of your personal information over the past 12 months by using our online webform to validate and submit your request at: [CCPA Online Webform](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/048df61e-d7fa-4291-a10d-715edb5fcb76/e03d430c-5779-4f72-9fcd-f4d82785861a).  You may also exercise these access and deletion rights by emailing [privacyrequests@jackpocket.com](mailto:privacyrequests@jackpocket.com). You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice in a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:
    
    * Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected Personal Information or an authorized representative of that person;
        
    * Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.  

These rights are not absolute, and in some instances, we may decline your request as permitted by law. We will need to verify your identity to process your access and deletion rights and reserve the right to confirm your California residency. To verify your identity, we may require you to log into your Jackpocket account (if applicable), provide government identification, give a declaration as to your identity under penalty of perjury, and/or provide additional information.   

Your authorized agent may make a request on your behalf upon our verification of the agent’s identity and our receipt of a copy of the valid power of attorney given to your authorized agent pursuant to California Probate Code Sections 4000-4465. If you have not provided your agent with such a power of attorney, you must provide your agent with written and signed permission to exercise your CCPA rights on your behalf, provide the information we request to verify your identity and provide us with written confirmation that you have given the authorized agent permission to submit the request.

**Shine the Light**

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California have the right to request from companies conducting business in California certain information regarding Jackpocket’s disclosure within the immediately preceding calendar year of that California resident’s personal information to third parties (and in some cases affiliates) for their direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, by disclosing in its privacy policy that it provides consumers choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties and affiliates for those third parties’ and affiliates’ direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice. We do not currently share personal information with third parties or affiliates for those third parties’ or affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. However, if we do so in the future, we intend to provide you with a choice prior to sharing your personal information with third parties and affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. If you do not opt-in or if you do not choose to opt-out at the time Jackpocket offers that choice, Jackpocket will not share your information with that identified third party or affiliate for its direct marketing purposes.

If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing information with third parties and affiliates for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice, please send your request to the following email address: privacyrequests@jackpocket.com.  You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your e-mail.

**How we respond to Do Not Track signals** 

California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how companies respond to "Do Not Track" browser settings. Jackpocket does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

### Children Under the Age of 13

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on or through our Services. If it is discovered that we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, this information will be deleted. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacyrequests@jackpocket.com.

Transactions through our Services are limited to those meeting the age requirements in the applicable jurisdiction.

### Information Security

The security of your personal information is extremely important. We maintain commercially reasonable technical, administrative, physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personal information provided to us, including encryption of your social security number, passwords and Payment Data. 

However, no communication over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Although we take care to protect your personal information, including a secure method of transfer for communications containing your Account Data or account number and robust encryption for all other communications, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us, so you do so at your own risk.

### Your Responsibilities 

The security of your information and account with us is also dependent on you. Please keep any account information, including access to your computer or mobile device secure. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality, accuracy and completeness of your account information. We also recommend that you log out of your account when you are done using our Services, to help prevent another party from accessing your account. If you believe your account has been compromised, you must notify us immediately at privacyrequests@jackpocket.com.

### Changes and Updates

This Privacy Policy may be periodically revised, and this will be reflected by the “Last update” date at the top. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. If a revision to this Privacy Policy, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you by contacting you through the email address associated with your account and/or we may provide notice to you within the app itself where we may require you to acknowledge such changes. For non-material changes, where your acknowledgement is not required, your continued use of the Services constitutes your acceptance of the Policy as amended. Each time you use the Services, the version of our Privacy Policy then posted will apply to that use, so it is your responsibility to check for updates each time you access the Services.

To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.

### Contact Us

Please contact Jackpocket with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy by emailing: privacyrequests@jackpocket.com. 

* 

* Jackpocket

* Blog

* Resources

© 2024 Jackpocket, Inc.

Number one ranked lottery app according to data from AppFollow. Must be 18 or older to play the lottery. 21+ in AZ. 19+ in NE. Jackpocket is not affiliated with any State Lottery. If you or someone you know has a gambling problem and wants help, residents of NY call 1-877-8-HOPE-NY or text HOPENY (467369); residents of MA call 1-800-327-5050; residents of OR call 1-877-MYLIMIT; residents of PR call 1-800-981-0023; all others, call 1-800-GAMBLER. The Winners Corner brand is owned by Jackpocket and operates as a licensed lottery retailer in various states. Please visit [Terms of Service](https://jackpocket.com/tos) for full terms of service.

### Try Jackpocket for free

Scan this QR code with your phone's camera to download the Jackpocket app.

Or just visit jackpocket.com on your mobile device to download.
